# Wendy Posella

North Hollywood, CA 91605 wendyposella4\_dby@indeedemail.com (818) 824-0227

Full Charge Bookkeeper. Methodical and Analytical organized with 15+ years of experience managing accounts and financial records. Dedicated to ensuring information is complete and error-free, with a sharp eye for pinpointing red flags and discrepancy. Proven record of reducing financial risk and boosting profits.

## Work Experience

## **Remote Bookkeeper**

Rhodes Restaurants LLC - Los Angeles, CA August 2016 to Present

#### Work P/T)

- · Worked from home office on-line banking
- Code receipts and enter invoices for 4 restaurants daily in QuickBooks
- Check accuracy of inventory against purchase orders weekly
- Communicate with vendors on payments and deliveries
- Processed checks payments and on-line payments.
- · Process employee time sheets monitoring daily time clock and ensure payroll is correct
- HR employee files.

## Office Manager

Affordable In-Home Health Care September 2018 to March 2020

- Interviewing potential personnel
- Scheduling matching candidates to open shifts
- Updating clients and personnel database
- Payroll using ADP and QuickBooks 200 employees
- Client invoicing and billing
- Answer all calls, Intake new clients
- Handle all scheduling and problem solve
- Filing confidential documents
- Ability to perform numerous tasks simultaneously
- Trustworthy in banking activity

## **Full Charge Bookkeeper**

Prime Point Contracting Sun Valley January 2016 to September 2018

- Set up company accounts on QuickBooks exported 3 years of data.
- Reconciled 3 years of bank statements
- Enter all invoices, bills, receipt
- · Weekly check runs

- Financial reports
- Track and monitor project progress
- Job costing and budgeting, Bank Draw
- Google drive, PO system, calendar.
- Communications via email, phone, text, memos, correspondence.
- · Coordinate with outside vendors and contractors.
- Insurance Certificates

ACCOUNTING Bella Home Care Services - Los Angeles, CA March 2012 to August 2016

- Accurately and efficiently processed weekly payroll for employees
- Designed report in ADP to audit the payroll, catching inaccuracies
- · Monitored check payments, identifying and resolving discrepancies immediately
- Bank Deposits
- · Client relations
- Bank Reconciliations
- Matched, Monitored and Scheduled all assignments
- Marketing, Client Intake

## **Property Supervisor**

Metro Investment Group January 2015 to January 2016

- Set up Companies accounts on Appfolio (Property Mgmt Accounting Software) Exported 3 years of Data
- Reconciled 3 years of bank statements
- Oversee and process accounts receivable for 200 residential units
- Instituted system to pull aging reports at more frequent intervals, quickly identifying and routinely tracking delinquent accounts, which reduced monthly outstanding debt by 50%
- Develop positive relations with vendors and tenants, addressing account inquiries as needed
- Performed weekly reconciliations for bank and credit card accounts, ensuring accurate records and identifying inconsistencies
- Generated reports, including income statements and balance sheets
- Prepared and delivered bank deposits
- Manage accounts payable and weekly check runs for main office
- Generate aging reports and contact 30+ clients on weekly basis to collect payment, reducing outstanding debt 60% in 4 months

## **Property Manager/bookkeeper**

Seltzer/Doren Property Mgmt - Los Angeles, CA April 2006 to August 2009

- Process monthly rent collections & maintain tenant ledgers for 900 residential units
- Monitored renovations and performed property inspections working closely with Maintenance staff.
- Coordinate with outside vendors scheduled and verify work orders
- Generate lease agreements and all other related documentation
- Run credit and criminal background checks on all prospect tenants.
- Survey rental market rates
- 3-Day Notice deliveries monitor calendar for court filing
- Annual Registration and Insurance

## **On-site Resident Manager/bookkeeper**

Sycamore Park and Heritage Park Apartments - Azusa, CA June 2003 to March 2006

- A/R, A/P, Bank Reconciliation
- Processing monthly rent collections for two buildings, total 220 units
- Move-in / Move-out inspections, security deposit itemization
- Process lease agreements and all other related contracts
- Background credit verification
- Issue 3-day Notices and correspondence
- Maintenance work orders and dispatch

## Education

## Master of Health Care Administration in Health Care Administration

Kaplan University School - Davenport, FL

December 2015

## **Bachelor of Science in Business Administration Concentration in Management**

Kaplan University - Davenport, FL

October 2012

## Skills

- Office Management/Daily Operations
- Construction Experience 5 years
- Communication
- Human Resources/Payroll ADP
- Property Management
- Finance/Accounting/Bookkeeping
- Microsoft Office
- Excel
- Appfolio
- QuickBooks Google Drive/Calendar